

SKILLS

CI/CD · GCP · Terraform · Kubernetes ·

Docker · Jenkins · CircleCi · Bash · git ·

Linux · Ansible

EDUCATION

Master Degree of lot and microservices

Kharkiv Aerospace University 2017 - 2018

Bachelor of Compute Engineering

Kryvij Rih National University 2013 - 2017

STRENGTHS

Engaging Personality

Engaging communicator, can be persuasive, but always listen carefully.

Delivering Results

Focus on the key inputs and deliver them with the right quality and in a timely fashion.

Efficient

Relying on a mix of problem-solving and time-management skills

VALERII VLASOV

Senior Devops Engineer

\ +380678398825 @ Kifocheg@gmail.com

@www.linkedin.com/in/valerii-vlasov-30b621198/

Kharkiv, Ukraine

SUMMARY

I am a Senior DevOps Engineer with almost 5 years expirience in different kind of projects. I have carried out maintenance and develop CI\CD infrastructure, terraform code, Kubernetes cluster and etc. I am open-minded, result-oriented, and self-motivated. I believe my experience helps me to create suitable infrastructure and automate routine tasks which will give the best possible result for the project.

EXPERIENCE

Middle - Senior DevOps Engineer

2021 - Ongoing Remote Ukraine

SoftServe

Worked on 3 different projects.

Participated in various activities as a member of the CloudOps team, such as strategic infrastructure/automation development, support of incoming requests from developers, support of the Data department, and various infrastructure improvements and automation.

Contributed to architecture and design.

Conducted requirements analysis and clarification.

Estimated, prioritized, and distributed tasks

Developed code.

Built and deployed development scripts.

 Tech stack: GCP, Terraform, Kubernetes, CircleCI, Spinnaker, Jenkins, Concord, Ansible, Snyk, helm

Junior - Middle DevOps Engineer

2019 - 2021 Kharkiv, Ukraine

EPAM Systems

Worked on 4 different projects.
 Was responsible for CI/CD pipelines, knowledge sharing, coaching, estimation, prioritization, and distribution of tasks, code development, product support, and

 documentation maintenance
 Tech stack: GCP, AWS, Terraform, Openshift, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Ansible, Custodian, Helm, Nexus, SonarQube, Gerrit, Python, Bash, Kibana, fluentbit, Prometheus.

SOFT SKILLS

Time management	Attention to Detail	
Active listening	Adaptability	

Powered by CO Enhancy www.enhancy.com